<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>theatreclub</title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Witness some of the West End’s biggest shows with our unrivalled London theatre break packages – complete with tickets and a hotel stay! You can even add return rail journey to your theatre break in London as well as tickets for the city’s leading attractions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t fancy London? Our regional theatre breaks offer you the chance to see the capital’s biggest shows hit the stage in key UK cities like Edinburgh, Manchester and Cardiff. Or, to really book a break to remember, experience a Broadway theatre break in New York with tickets, hotel and flights included in your package!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    <link>http://theatreclub.superbreak.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://theatreclub.superbreak.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 17:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 17:17:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Motown The Musical</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Experience the magic of Motown on a Super Break Motown The Musical Theatre Break!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;about-motown-the-musical&quot;&gt;About Motown The Musical&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Featuring an incredible selection of Motown’s most recognisable hits, Motown The Musical is certain to have audiences dancing in the aisles. World-conquering songs including ‘Dancing In The Street’, ‘Ain’t No Mountain High Enough’ and ‘I Heard It Through The Grapevine’ are just a few of the 50 hits that appear in the show performed by an eighteen piece orchestra. A treat for music-lovers and theatre fans alike, Motown The Musical at London’s Shaftesbury Theatre is simply not to be missed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-story&quot;&gt;The Story&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a story spanning a number of decades, Motown The Musical tells the amazing tale of the man who broke down the barriers and fought against all odds to define a generation. Discover the story behind the sound that changed opinions, touched lives and took the world by storm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set to much-loved hits from the Motown era, follow the unlikely success story of once aspiring boxer and Motown record label founder Berry Gordy as he discovers talents like Smokey Robinson, The Supremes, Marvin Gaye and Michael Jackson. With a story spanning a number of decades, the audience will discover the truth of Motown’s rise to fame, and the personal dramas behind the soundtrack of a generation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-book-motown-the-musical-with-super-break&quot;&gt;Why Book Motown The Musical with Super Break?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We at Super Break have been providing short breaks within the UK and Europe for over 30 years, and have built up relationships over this time to get our customers the best deals on offer. On a Motown the Musical theatre break with Super Break, you can save up to 30% with our top price saver tickets, meaning you get one of the best seats in the house and great deal on your ticket &amp;amp; hotel package.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;awards--what-do-the-critics-think&quot;&gt;Awards &amp;amp; What Do The Critics Think?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Motown The Musical received four Tony Award nominations, one of which for best orchestration. Patricia Wilcox, who oversaw the choreography received an Astaire award for Outstanding Choreographer of a Broadway Show in 2013.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Something close to rapture spreads through the audience” the New York Times recalls, while CBS defines it as “More than a Broadway show… a celebration of music that transformed America”. According to the Hollywood Reporter, “There’s no denying the power and energy of the show’s arsenal of killer tunes. There’s an enormous kick of watching them perform live that no iPod playlist can match”.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://theatreclub.superbreak.com/motown</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://theatreclub.superbreak.com/motown</guid>
        
        
        <category>Shows</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lion King</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;about-disneys-the-lion-king&quot;&gt;About Disney’s The Lion King&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be transported to the Serengeti plains with a Lion King theatre break to see the wonderful music and magic of the famous Disney Musical. Celebrating a staggering 16 years in London, the show is famous for its funky African rhythms, incredible puppetry and special effects that bring the jungle to life on stage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-story&quot;&gt;The Story&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Lion King begins with a huge musical celebration – born to the King of the Jungle Mufasa, Simba is the new hope and heir to his father’s throne. Not everyone is happy; Simba’s jealous Uncle Scar laments his lost chance to be king and plots to kill both Mufasa and Simba. As we watch Simba grow up – with a little help from his friends Timon and Pumbaa – he must finally decide whether to return to the kingdom and try to reclaim his rightful place as The Lion King.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;history-of-disneys-the-lion-king&quot;&gt;History of Disney’s The Lion King&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twenty years after the incredibly popular film, The Lion King lives on at London’s Lyceum Theatre. With a string of awards and an incredible soundtrack that is as fantastic as it is familiar, The Lion King is a huge hit with both audiences and critics, with over 75 million people worldwide having seen and fallen in love with this spectacular production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note: Children under 3 years of age are not permitted to enter the Lyceum Theatre. The Lion King is recommended for ages 6 and up. Parents/guardians may be asked to remove persistently noisy or rowdy children. All persons aged 16 or under must be accompanied by an adult and may not sit on their own within the auditorium. All persons entering the theatre, regardless of age, must have a ticket.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://theatreclub.superbreak.com/lion-king</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://theatreclub.superbreak.com/lion-king</guid>
        
        
        <category>Shows</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Les Miserables</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;about-les-misérables&quot;&gt;About Les Misérables&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les Misérables London is renowned as the longest running musical of all time. It is the powerful story of ex-convict Jean Valjean and his attempts to re-enter into a society that has abandoned him. Set in 19th Century France amidst the struggles of the French revolution, Les Misérables the musical is a tale of passion, love and broken dreams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-story&quot;&gt;The Story&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After 19 years in prison Jean Valjean is a free man, yet marked by his parole papers he is made an outcast. In an attempt to start his life anew Jean Valjean changes his name and moves away, breaking his parole. Pursued by Inspector Javert the two men’s lives interweave as their paths cross time and time again. With an array of emotive characters, driving plot twists and impressive songs Les Misérables the musical has placed itself firmly in the hearts of its audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;history-of-les-misérables&quot;&gt;History of Les Misérables&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now at the Queens Theatre London, Les Misérables has been seen by more than 65 million people worldwide in 44 countries and in 21 languages, this spectacular adaptation of Victor Hugo’s masterpiece continues to thrill audiences night after night.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://theatreclub.superbreak.com/les-miserables</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://theatreclub.superbreak.com/les-miserables</guid>
        
        
        <category>Shows</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dreamgirls</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After a hit run on Broadway, Dreamgirls is currently playing to packed houses in London’s West End.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;about-dreamgirls&quot;&gt;About Dreamgirls&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The glamorous theatre show, Dreamgirls won six Tony Awards in its opening year on Broadway, and is now well established in London’s West End. Directed by Tony-and Olivier-award-winning Broadway director, Casey Nicholaw, the show is set to be a big hit with an explosive soundtrack including hits like, ‘I Am Changing’, ‘Listen’ and ‘Dreamgirls’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-story&quot;&gt;The Story&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set in 1960’s America, during the revolutionary era of R&amp;amp;B, Dreamgirls tells the tale of a girl group from Chicago called ‘The Dreams’. Competing in lots of competitions, the girls come across Curtis Taylor, an ex- car salesman who wants to be their manager, and although the group finds initial success, rifts form in the band as Curtis tries to replace the current lead singer, Effie, with her best friend, Deena.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;history-of-dreamgirls&quot;&gt;History of Dreamgirls&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Opening on Broadway in 1981, the show was directed by Michael Bennett and starred Sheryl Lee Ralph, Jennifer Holiday and Loretta Devine as the three ‘Dreamgirls’. In 2006, the hit musical was adapted into a film starring Beyonce Knowles as Deena and Jennifer Hudson as Effie. The film won three Golden Globes and two Oscars, as well as winning supporting actress Hudson an Academy Award.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://theatreclub.superbreak.com/dreamgirls</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://theatreclub.superbreak.com/dreamgirls</guid>
        
        
        <category>Shows</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
